ubcbotanicalgarden.org 2010-11-18

# Website Privacy Policy

**Home** / Privacy Policy 

* * *

## Forums and Mailing Lists

When you share your email address with UBC Botanical Garden and Centre for Plant Research for either the email newsletters or the discussion forums, UBC Botanical Garden and Centre for Plant Research agrees to: 

  * Use your email address solely for UBC Botanical Garden and Centre for Plant Research purposes and communications;
  * Never sell or rent your email address or personal information with anyone;
  * Never share your email address or personal information with anyone except when required to pursue legal or disciplinary action subsequent to a contravention of the user agreement made when registering for the forums, **or** when ordered to by a court of law, **or** when permission has been expressly sought from you to share such information for a particular purpose;
  * Restrict the availabity of the email addresses and any private information in the mailing list and forums to employees of the University of British Columbia for purposes of managing the mailing lists and forums, for contacting you or for sending you emails based on your request for information or participation in the forums.

In addition, to the best of its abilities, UBC Botanical Garden and Centre for Plant Research will endeavour to prevent theft or access to email addresses and personal information from attacks on its server or databases. 

* * *

## Specifically for the Discussion Forums

Please be aware that some information disclosed when registering for and participating on the University of British Columbia Botanical Garden and Centre for Plant Research forums is public (e.g., location or information you choose to share when participating on the forums). You should exercise caution on how you choose to disclose that information. Please note that if the "email this user" form is used in the forums to send an email to another user, then the sender's email address will be displayed to the recipient. 

* * *

## A Note on Cookies

Cookies (small files which reside on your hard drive and contain information relating to a site) are used in the UBC Botanical Garden and Centre for Plant Research forums for better user interaction with the forums (for example, removing the necessity to log in every time or tracking which forums have been updated since you last visited). For better anonymity, accepting cookies can be turned off in your web browser, but it will hamper the user experience. 

* * *

## Previous versions of the Privacy Policy
